furtadosonline.com 2018-08-03

# www.furtadosonline.com : Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The security of personal information about you is our priority. We protect this information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet applicable law. We train our employees in the proper handling of personal information. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. 

##  How we use your Information

Furtados uses your personal information to provide you with services and to help us better understand your needs and interests. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits, to personalize promotional offers. Occasionally we may also use your information to contact you for market research regarding Furtados products or services. Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Furtados has built for itself a reputation of trust worthiness with a strong emphasis on quality and customer service, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. Our privacy practices are designed to provide protection for your personal information, all over the world. 

##  Access to and accuracy of your information

Furtados strives to keep your personal information accurate. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to maintain customer data accuracy. We will provide you with access to your information, including making reasonable effort to provide you with online access and the opportunity to change your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. 

##  Links to Non-Furtados websites

The Furtadosonline websites may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Furtados website. Furtados does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from us. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to give to third parties is not covered by the Furtados Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with Furtados; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy. 

##  Children's Privacy

We encourage children and minors (under the age of 18) to use our site for information and material. However, if you are under the age of 18, you cannot purchase any product on the site. If you wish to purchase a product on the site such purchase may be made by your legal guardian or parents who have registered as users of the site. 

##  Keeping your information secure

Furtados is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Furtadosonline has in place appropriate physical and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. 

##  Security

Furtadosonline Secure Shopping Guarantee protects you every time you shop at Furtados so that you never have to worry about the safety of your credit card information. We use the industry standard encryption protocol known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to keep your order information secure. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window. Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment and are not used for other purposes. We guarantee that every transaction you make at furtadosonline will be safe and secure. 

##  Modifications to Privacy Statement

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain of www.furtadosonline.com. By visiting our website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or register with our site Furtadosonline may modify this privacy statement at any juncture. If a material change is made to this Privacy Policy and/or the way we use our users' personally identifiable information, then we will post prominent notice of the nature of such change on the first page of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for reviewing this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes to it. Your continued use of the Site indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.
